basefarm.net 2017-06-29

# Basefarm | Privacy Policy

### **PRIVACY POLICY BASEFARM**

1.               INTRODUCTION

Basefarm is committed to protect and respect your privacy. With this privacy policy Basefarm describes how it ensures that your personal data and other data is processed in accordance with applicable data protection laws and cookie legislation.

2.               DATA CONTROLLER

Basefarm AS, reg. no. 982 211 743, Nydalen Allé 37a, 0484 Oslo, Norway, is the data controller in relation to personal data being processed on the Norwegian and English versions of the website.  
Basefarm AB, reg. no. 556638-0639, Sveavägen 159, 113 46 Stockholm, Sweden, is the data controller in relation to personal data being processed on the Swedish version of the website.  
Basefarm BV reg. no. [•], Beechavenue 106, 1119 PP Schiphol-Rijk, Netherlands, is the data controller in relation to personal data being processed on the Dutch version of the website.

The aforementioned Basefarm entities are collectively referred to as “Basefarm” in the following. You will find Basefarm’s contact information under section 10.

3.               WHEN DOES BASEFARM COLLECT PERSONAL DATA?

When you or your employer sets up an account or signs up for Basefarm’s newsletter;  
When you apply for a job at Basefarm or otherwise send a job application to Basefarm;  
In the event you turn to Basefarm with inquiries or requests via e-mail or telephone; and  
If you have accepted the use of cookies, Basefarm may also collect your IP address. For more information about Basefarm’s use of cookies, please see section 12.

4\.               WHAT DATA MAY BASEFARM COLLECT?

The personal data Basefarm may collect includes information about your name and contact details such as address, telephone number and e-mail address, company and any other information you provide. If you apply for a job at Basefarm, Basefarm will process your CV as well as any other information you attach with your application.

5.               HOW DOES BASEFARM PROCESS PERSONAL DATA?

The personal data collected by Basefarm is used to manage customer relations, assess potential employees and assist customers and website visitors with any requests or inquiries made on the website. The information may also be used for monitoring and development of Basefarm’s business and website, for example by analyzing statistics of website visitors, and to protect Basefarm’s rights.

If you apply for a job, Basefarm only uses your personal data for the purposes for which you provided the information. However, Basefarm may save interesting applications even after the recruitment period is over. Such applications may also be transferred to other entities within the Basefarm group.

6.               TO WHOM MAY BASEFARM DISCLOSE THE INFORMATION?

Basefarm will not sell, lease or otherwise transfer any personal data collected to a third party. Basefarm may however transfer the personal data to other companies within the Basefarm group or to business partners if it is necessary to fulfil its obligations towards you.

Personal data may be disclosed if it is necessary to:

a)         Comply with applicable law, regulation or similar or to comply with a legal process, request or order from an executive authority;

b)         defend Basefarm’s legal interests; or to

c)         detect, prevent, or otherwise avoid fraud, security breaches or technical issues.

7.               LINKS TO EXTERNAL WEBSITES

Basefarm’s website may contain links to third-party websites. Basefarm is not responsible for the processing of your personal data on such websites.

8\.               AMENDMENTS

If this policy is amended, Basefarm will publish the amended policy at [www.basefarm.com](http://www.basefarm.com/) with information about when the amendments will enter into force. If Basefarm carry out any significant changes to the policy, Basefarm may choose to inform by e-mail or by publishing a message on the website.

9.               THE RIGHT TO INFORMATION AND RECIFICATIONS

You have the right to require information about what personal data Basefarm is processing about you and for what purposes. You are also entitled to have any incomplete or inaccurate data rectified, erased or blocked. Please see the contact information in section 10 should you have any questions about how Basefarm processes your personal data.

10.             BASEFARM’S CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions relating to Basefarm’s processing of personal data, or if you want to invoke your right to access data, please contact relevant Basefarm entity on the address set out below:

Norway/Global:  
Basefarm AS  
PO Box 4488  
Nydalen  
0403 Oslo

Sweden:  
Basefarm AB  
Sveavägen 159  
113 46 Stockholm

Netherlands:  
Basefarm BV  
Beechavenue 106  
1119 PP Schiphol-Rijk

11.             SECURITY MEASURES

Basefarm has taken the organizational and technical security measures required to protect personal data against unauthorized access, modification and deletion.
